(MR) Goh Shao Yi

Singapore Citizen

Availability: Full-Time from Nov 2024 onwards

Email shaoyigoh@hotmail.com

Personal Site

https://shaodude.github.io/

Executive Summary

I am highly motivated and a fast learner with a keen eye for design. My passion and experience in software development and business allows me to understand core business needs and deliver visually compelling software solutions that helps businesses and end-users.

Education

Singapore Institute of Management - University of London (UOL)

Oct 2021 – Oct 2024 (Expected)

BSc Computer Science, First Class Honours (Expected)

Singapore Polytechnic (SP)

Apr 2015 – Mar 2018

Diploma in Banking and Finance

Work Experience

Director, Openwork Pte. Ltd.

Jan 2021 - Current

- Lead business development initiatives for home staging, furnishing, and minor renovation projects.
- Manage client interactions, including conducting meetings, performing in-depth research and evaluations, and crafting compelling pitches to showcase contextual value of services.
- Oversee project management from concept to completion, ensuring quality and client satisfaction through effective coordination and execution.
- Professionally manage and resolve conflicts that arise during operational activities, ensuring a positive representation of the company.

Software Development Intern, Leaptechnology Pte. Ltd.

Nov 2023 – Apr 2024

Key Technologies: Vue 3, TypeScript/ JavaScript, MYSQL, Tailwind CSS, Ionic, Vite, Pinia, GIT

- Core development team for SaaS CRM web application. Building frontend features in Vue and integrating existing backend APIs developed in PHP Laravel. building and fixing both frontend and backend code as needed.
- Engage with clients to showcase value and potential of software applications. Brainstorm and implement innovative features to enhance applications, driving continuous evolution and client satisfaction.
- Developed a multi-platform (IOS/ Android) workflow system mobile application (Vue Ionic) for a security company. The mobile app primarily serves as a platform for security officers to perform operation processes.
- Directly involved in the development of SQL database to accommodate evolving project requirements.

Finance Executive, Singapore Ministry of Trade & Industry (MTI)

Sep 2020 – Sep 2021

- Implemented a UiPath automation solution (RPA) for a financial process, saving over 70 hours annually.
- Designed and built an Excel database to efficiently consolidate physical invoices electronically.

Relevant Coursework

Final Year Project - Task Manager Mobile Application Ft. Custom Task Prioritization algorithm

Relevant Knowledge: React Native, Redux JS, Google Firebase, Expo, Jest Testing, User Testing

Website Development [Grade A]

Relevant Knowledge: HTML, CSS, JS, Express JS, Node JS, SQL, SQLite3, Bootstrap 5

Machine Learning & Neural Networks [Grade A]

Relevant Knowledge: Python, scikit-learn, TensorFlow, NumPy, Pandas, Seaborn, Matplotlib, Selenium

Profile

Certifications

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner, UiPath RPA Developer Foundation

Sports

• Floorball – Singapore University Games SUniG 2023 (Bronze Medal), IVP Games 2024

Language Proficiency

• English (Native), Mandarin (Intermediate)